medicalconnections.com 2013-10-05

# Privacy | physical therapy, pt, ot, nurse, pta, travel jobs, perm jobs | Medical Connections

You are truly remarkable and have been a pleasure to work with.  John G. & Sarah M., Los Angeles, CA

We, Medical Connections, have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This privacy statement discloses the information collection and disclosure practices for our Web site. By accessing this Site, you consent to the collection and use of information as described herein.

**WHO WE ARE:** Our Site(s) provides you with various services related to travel, temporary and permanent employment opportunities. In order to provide these services, we collect information from you a job seeker through our Sites and forward it on to one or more third party service providers that use the information to provide you with these services. If you are a seeking employment, we collect personally identifying information from you through our Sites, including but not limited to your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and information about career preferences. In order for us to provide these services, we also may collect supplementary personally identifying information about you from third party sources to correct or supplement the information we have requested from you.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION:** [www.medicalconnections.com](http://www.medicalconnections.com/ "Medical Connections") is a career site, you, the visitor, have the option of posting your resume in our database. Posting your resume can have significant benefits, as it can be viewed by a large number of facilities, staffing companies, recruiting firms, and travel companies. Depending on your qualifications and your position requirements, you may receive many contacts from facilities, recruiting firms, staffing companies, and travel companies. Contacts may be made by phone, mail, fax, and/or email. Any email contacts are not spam, and by posting your resume, you agree not to submit any email you receive due to posting your resume as spam.

**UPDATING INFORMATION:** At which point you no longer wish to receive contacts, you may remove your resume from our database. If you are currently employed, there is a chance that your current employer will receive your resume if they are a preferred client of [www.medicalconnections.com](http://www.medicalconnections.com/ "Medical Connections"). If this concerns you, do not post your resume. [www.medicalconnections.com](http://www.medicalconnections.com/ "Medical Connections") will not be held responsible for any damages if your current employer receives, or views your resume.

**POSTING INFORMATION:** By posting your resume you acknowledge the acceptance of this disclaimer. Information is not required to view jobs. If you prefer to simply search jobs, and respond to those of interest without posting your resume to our database, feel free to do so.

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION:** Except as set forth in this privacy statement, we do not disclose, sell, rent, loan, trade or lease any personally identifying information collected at our Sites beyond our current client(s).

**LINKS:** Please be aware that we may provide links to third party Web sites from our Sites as a service to our users and we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites. We have no ability to control the privacy and data collection practices of such sites and the privacy policies of such sites may differ from that of [www.medicalconnections.com](http://www.medicalconnections.com/ "Medical Connections"), Therefore, we encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies of such sites before providing them with any information.

**COOKIES AND WEB TRACKING:** To enhance your experience with [www.medicalconnections.com](http://www.medicalconnections.com/ "Medical Connections"), we use a feature on your internet browser called a "cookie". Cookies are small tracking files that your web browser uses to allow applying for multiple positions without the hassle of having to re-enter your information each time you wish to apply. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results, and a more personalized site experience. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this will hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on our site.

**SECURITY:** We [www.medicalconnections.com](http://www.medicalconnections.com/ "Medical Connections") use reasonable security measures to store and maintain personally identifying information to protect it from loss, misuse, alternation or destruction by any unauthorized party while it is under our control.

**CHILDREN:** We do not intend, and these Sites are not designed, to collect personal information from children under the age of 18. If you are under 18 years old, you should not register for our services or otherwise provide information on our Sites.

**CHOICE AND ACCESS:** [www.medicalconnections.com](http://www.medicalconnections.com/ "Medical Connections") gives users the following options for accessing, changing and deleting personal information previously provided, or opting out of receiving communications from us:

  * Email us at [info@medicalconnections.com](mailto:info@medicalconnections.com) or
  * Call us at the following telephone number: (866) 681-2056

**QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS:** If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy statement, the practices of our Sites, or your dealings with our Sites, please contact us at the following address or email us at [info@medicalconnections.com](mailto:info@medicalconnections.com)

Medical Connections, Inc.

2300 Glades Rd. 202E, Boca Raton, FL 33431
